Guide to the Frauke Heard-Bey and David Heard collection AD.MC.064
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Government publications, 1968-2007
  - Abu Dhabi emirate: al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah = Official Gazette, 1972-2006
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 15, 21 June 1973 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 16, 28 June 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 17, 5 July 1973 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 18, 12 July 1973 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 19, 19 July 1973 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette).Year 2, No. 20, 26 July 1973 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 21, 2 August 1973 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 22, 9 August 1973 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 23, 16 August 1973 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 24, 23 August 1973 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 25, 30 August 1973 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 26, 6 September 1973 / 9 Sha'aban 1393 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 27, 13 September 1973 / 16 Sha'aban 1393 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 28, 20 September 1973 / 23 Sha'aban 1393 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 29, 27 September 1973 / 1 Ramadan 1393 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 30, 4 September 1973 / 8 Ramadan 1393 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 31, 11 September 1973 / 15 Ramadan 1393 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 32, 18 September 1973 / 22 Ramadan 1393 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 33, 25 September 1973 / 29 Ramadan 1393 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 34, 1 November 1973 / 2 Shuwwan (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 35, 8 November 1973 / 13 Shuwwan 1393 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 36, 15 November 1973 / 20 Shuwwan 1393 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 37, 22 November 1973 / 27 Shuwan 1393 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 38, 29 November 1973 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 39, 2 December 1973 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 40, 13 December 1973 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 41, 20 December 1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 42, 27 December 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 43, 10 January 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 44, 17 January 1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 1, 24 January 1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 2, 31 January 1974 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 3, 7 February 1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 4, 14 February 1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 5, 21 February 1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 6, 28 February 1974 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 7, 7 March 1974 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 8, 14 March 1974 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 9, 21 March 1974 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 10, 28 March 1974 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 11, 4 April 1974 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 12, 11 April 1974 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 13, 18 April 1974 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 14, 25 April 1974 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 15, 2 May 1974 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 16, 9 May 1974 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 17, 16 May 1974 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 18, 23 May 1974 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 19, 30 May 1974 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 20, 2 June 1974 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 21, 13 June 1974 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 22, 20 June 1974 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 23, 27 June 1974 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 24, 4 July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 25, 11 July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 26, 18 July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 3, No. 27, 25 July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 1, 2 January 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 2, 2 February 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 3, 1 March 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 4, 1 April 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 5, 1 May 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 6, 1 June 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 7, 1 July 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 8, 2 August 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 9, 1 September 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 10, 1 October 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 11, 1 November 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 9, No. 12, 1 December 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 1, 3 January 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 2, 1 February 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 3, 1 March 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 4, 1 April 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 5, 2 May 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 6, 1 June 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 7, 1 July 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 8, 4 August 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 9, 1 September 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 10, 1 November 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 10, No. 11, 1 December 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 11, No. 1, 16 January 1982
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 11, No. 4, 1 April 1982
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 11, No. 5, 1 May 1982
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 11, No. 6, 1 June 1982
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 11, No. 7, 1 July 1982
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 1, January 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 2, February 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 3, March 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 4, April 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 5, May 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 6, June 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 7, July 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 8, August 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 9, September 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 10, October 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 11, November 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 21, No. 12, December 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 22, No. 1, January 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 22, No. 2, February 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 22, No. 3, March 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 22, No. 5, May 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 22, No. 6, June 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 22, No. 7, July 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 22, No. 8, August 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 22, No. 9, September 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 22, No. 10, October 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 22, No. 11, November 1993
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 1996: January - June (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 1996: July - December (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 1997: January - June (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 1997: July - December (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 1998: January - June (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 1998: July - December (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 2004: February - June (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 2004: July - December (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 2005: January - June (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 2005: July - November (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Official Gazette: English translation (excerpts), 2006: January - November (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - United Arab Emirates government: general, 1972-2000
    - Annual Statistical Bulletin of Agriculture and Fisheries For the Years 1984 and 1985 = al-Nashrat al-iḥṣāʼīyah al-sanawīyah li-qitạ̄ʻ al-zirāʻah wa-al-tharwah al-samakīyah (Ministry of Agriculture & Fisheries), August 1987 (Volume 48)
      General
      HD2061.5 .N373 1985
    - Annual Insurance Statistics, 1986 (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Volume 49)
      HG8695.45 .I37 1986
    - Annual Insurance Statistics, 1989 (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Volume 50)
      HG8695.45 .I37 1989
    - Annual Statistical Abstract, 1976 = Majmūʻah al-iḥṣāʼīyah al-sanawīyah (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.) (Volume 51)
      HA4566.A25a 1976
    - Annual Statistical Abstract, 1977 = Majmūʻah al-iḥṣāʼīyah al-sanawīyah (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.) (Volume 52)
      HA4566 .A25a 1977
    - Annual Statistical Abstract, 1985 = Majmūʻah al-iḥṣāʼīyah al-sanawīyah (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Volume 53)
      HA4566 .A25a 1985
    - Annual Statistical Abstract, 1991 = Majmūʻah al-iḥṣāʼīyah al-sanawīyah (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Volume 54)
      HA4566 .A25a 1991
    - Annual Statistical Abstract, 1992 = Majmūʻah al-iḥṣāʼīyah al-sanawīyah (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Volume 55)
      HA4566 .A25a 1992
    - [Economic and Social Developments in the UAE during the years 1985-1990] = Al-taṭawarāt al-iqtiṣāḍīyah wa al-ijtimāʻīyah fī dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttaḥidah, lil-sanawāt 1985-1990 (Ministry of Planning), 1993 (Volume 56)
    - [Education in the United Arab Emirates] = al-Taʻlīm fī Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Mutaḥḥidah (Ministry of Education), [November 1975] (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - al-Fihris al-jāmiʻ li-wathāʼiq Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttaḥidah: al-majalid al-awal [Index to the collected documents of the United Arab Emirates: the first councils], 1972-1980 (Volume 73)
      DS247.T8 A38 Index
    - Foreign Trade Statistics 1984 = Iḥṣāʼāt al-tijārah al-khārijīyah (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Volume 124)
      HF3766 .A355 1984
    - Foreign Trade Statistics 1985 = Iḥṣāʼāt al-tijārah al-khārijīyah (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Volume 57)
      HF3766 .A355 1985
    - Foreign Trade Statistics 1991 = Iḥṣāʼāt al-tijārah al-khārijīyah (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Volume 58)
      HF3766.A355 1991
    - [Leadership and Youth] = al-Qāʼid wa-al-shabāb: fī munāsabat al-iḥtifāl bi-al-ʻīd al-waṭanī al-ʻishrīn (Wizārat al-Shabāb wa-al-Riyāḍah / Ministry of Youth and Recreation), December 2, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Nashrah iḥṣā'īyah al-ta'alīm = Statistical Bulletin of Education (Ministry of Education), 1974-1975 (Volume 63)
    - National Accounts for United Arab Emirates, 1975-1984 = al-Ḥisābāt al-qawmīyah li-Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttaḥidah (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Planning Department), 1985 (Volume 59)
    - Statistical Abstract of Social Affairs = al-Majmūʻah al-iḥṣāʼīyah lil-shūʼūn al-ijtimāʻīyah (UAE. Ministry of Labour and Social Affairs. Studies, Researches and Statistic Unit), 2000 (Volume 60)
      HV381.5 .A35 2000
    - [Telephone directory of government officials], 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - UAE. Code of Civil Procedure [Arabic], March 1992
    - UAE. Provisional Constitution. Undated [Arabic] (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Vital Statistics. Births and Deaths 1980 = Iḥṣāʼāt al-ḥayawīyah. Mawālīd wa-al-wafayāt (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Volume 61)
      HA4566.A14 1980
    - Vital Statistics. Births and Deaths 1991 = Iḥṣāʼāt al-ḥayawīyah. Mawālīd wa-al-wafayāt (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Volume 63)
      HA4566 .A14 1991
    - Wathā'iq: Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Mutaḥḥidah = [Documents, United Arab Emirates] (Center for Documentation and Research, Abu Dhabi), 1972 (Volume 64)
      DS247.T8 A38 1972
    - Wathā'iq: Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Mutaḥḥidah = [Documents, United Arab Emirates] (Center for Documentation and Research, Abu Dhabi), 1973 (Volume 65)
      DS247.T8 A38 1973
    - Wathā'iq: Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Mutaḥḥidah = [Documents, United Arab Emirates] (Center for Documentation and Research, Abu Dhabi), 1974 (Volume 66)
      DS247.T8 A38 1974
    - Wathā'iq: Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Mutaḥḥidah = [Documents, United Arab Emirates] (Center for Documentation and Research, Abu Dhabi), 1975 (Volume 67)
      DS247.T8 A38 1975
    - Wathā'iq: Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Mutaḥḥidah = [Documents, United Arab Emirates] (Center for Documentation and Research, Abu Dhabi), 1976 (Volume 68)
      DS247.T8 A38 1976
    - Wathā'iq: Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Mutaḥḥidah = [Documents, United Arab Emirates] (Center for Documentation and Research, Abu Dhabi), 1977 (Volume 69)
      DS247.T8 A38 1977
    - Wathā'iq: Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Mutaḥḥidah = [Documents, United Arab Emirates] (Center for Documentation and Research, Abu Dhabi), 1978 (Volume 70)
      DS247.T8 A38 1978
    - Wathā'iq: Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Mutaḥḥidah = [Documents, United Arab Emirates] (Center for Documentation and Research, Abu Dhabi), 1979 (Volume 71)
      DS247.T8 A38 1979
    - Wathā'iq: Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Mutaḥḥidah = [Documents, United Arab Emirates] (Center for Documentation and Research, Abu Dhabi), 1980 (Volume 72)
      1980
    - Yearly Bulletin, Retail and Wholesale Prices, 1992 = al-Nashrah al-sanawīyah lil-asʻār, tajziʼah wa-jumlah ( UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Department). (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Yearly Hotels Statistic Bulletin 1992 = al-Nashrah al-sanawīyah li-iḥṣāʼ al-fanādiq (UAE. Ministry of Planning. Central Statistical Dept.). (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - United Arab Emirates government: Central Bank and Currency Board, 1974-2003
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Annual Report 31st, December 1982 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Annual Report 31st, December 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Annual Report, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Annual Report, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Annual Report, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Annual Report, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Annual Report, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Annual Report, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - United Arab Emirates. Central Bank. Annual Report, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Central Bank of the United Arab Emirates. Goals and Achievements, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Central Bank. Annual Report [Arabic version], 1987 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Central Bank. Annual Report [Arabic version], 1991 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Central Bank. Annual Report [Arabic version], 1992 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Bulletin vol 2, no. 1, December 1981 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - United Arab Emirates. Central Bank Bulletin vol 2, no. 2, June 1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - United Arab Emirates. Central Bank Bulletin vol 6, no. 2, June 1986 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Bulletin vol 7, no. 1, December 1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Bulletin, June 1987 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Bulletin, June 1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Bulletin, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Bulletin, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Bulletin, June 1992 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - United Arab Emirates Central Bank Bulletin, June 1993 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - UAE. Central Bank. Economic Bulletin [Arabic], Vol. 1, Issue 1, Dec. 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - UAE. Central Bank. Economic Bulletin [Arabic], Vol. 2, Issue 1, Dec. 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - UAE. Central Bank. Economic Bulletin [Arabic], Vol. 2, Issue 2, June 1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - UAE. Central Bank. Economic Bulletin [Arabic], Vol. 3, Issue 1, December 1982 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - UAE. Central Bank. Economic Bulletin [Arabic], Dec. 1986. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - UAE. Central Bank. Economic Bulletin [Arabic], June 1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - United Arab Emirates. Central Bank. Statistical Supplement, Sept. 1982 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - United Arab Emirates. Central Bank. Statistical Supplement, March 1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - United Arab Emirates. Central Bank. Statistical Supplement, September 1987 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - United Arab Emirates. Central Bank. Statistical Bulletin, Jul-Sept 2003 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Annual Report 31st, December 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Annual Report 31st, December 1977 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Annual Report 31st, December 1978 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Annual Report 31st, December 1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Bulletin vol 1. no. 1, November 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Bulletin vol 1. no. 2, May 1975 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Bulletin vol 2. no. 1, November 1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Bulletin vol 2. no. 2, May 1976 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Bulletin vol 3. no. 1, November 1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Bulletin vol 3, no. 2, May 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Bulletin vol 4, no. 1, November 1977 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Bulletin vol 4, no. 2, May 1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Bulletin vol 5, no. 1, December 1978 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - United Arab Emirates Currency Board Bulletin vol 6, no. 1, December 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - United Arab Emirates government: Official Gazette, and related (Arabic), 1971-1995
    - al-ʻAdālah: majallah qānūnīyah = [Justice Magazine] (Abu Dhabi: Ministry of Justice) Issue 3, Year 1, July 1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - al-ʻAdālah: majallah qānūnīyah = [Justice Magazine] (Abu Dhabi: Ministry of Justice), Issue 6, Year 2, April 1975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - al-Majmūʻat al-ūlā lil-qawānīn al-ittiḥādīya = [First Collection of Laws of the Federation], [1971-1973] (Volume 74)
    - Majmūʻat al-qawānīn wa-'l-marasīm li-dawlat al-Imārāt al-Arabīya al-Muttaḥida [Collection of laws and decrees of the UAE], 1974 (Volume 75)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Issue 1, Year 1, December 1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Issue 2, Year 2, March 1972 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Issue 3, Year 2, May 1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Issue 4, Year 2, July 1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Issue 5, Year 2, July 1972 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Issue 6, Year 2, September 1972 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Issue 7, Year 2, November 1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Issue 8, Year 3, February 1973 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Issue 9, Year 3, March 1973 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette): Issue 21, Year 4, August 1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 75, Year 10, January 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 76, Year 10, February 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 77, Year 10, March 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 78, Year 10, April 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 79, Year 10, April 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 80, Year 10, May 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 81, Year 10, July1980